search-solver.com 2010-06-21

# Search-Solver - Start searching!

**PRIVACY POLICY SEARCH-SOLVER ENGINE**

The following Privacy Policy covers the personal data processing activities undertaken by Favorit Network as provider of the service, Search-Solver. You can always contact us at

Favorit Network SL  
Rambla Catalunya 12 2-2  
Barcelona 08007  
Spain

or via our contact form [Contact](http://www.search-solver.com/index.php?footpage=contact&lg=EN)

**1\. Collected Data**

When you use our service, Search-Solver, the Provider will collect your _IP address_ but will not use it for any identification purpose. It will be stored in a server log. These server logs may also include information such as browser type, browser language, and the date and time of your request.  
Search-Solver will record the _keywords_ searched by you without any identification purpose but just with the purpose of generating aggregate data.   
We may also present _links_ in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. 

**2\. Purpose of Processing**

The data from web logs will be used for the sole purposes of analysing trends and for IT-security purposes.  
We will not process any personal data or use any information to create a user profile or track preferences. Information will be processed only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy 

**3\. Duration of Storage**

Log files are stored for 14 days in the Common Log File (CLF) format. The other types of data will be kept for two years.

**4\. Cookies**

Search-Solver service uses cookies to record the 'color theme' and language selection. Cookies are small files that are used by Search-Solver and are stored in your computer. We do not store any further personal information. You can still refuse cookies via the options of your browser.

**5\. Disclosure of your Data**

Any personal data will be disclosed only after requesting you with and opt-in consent.

**6\. Service Providers**

We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns.

**7\. Your Individual Rights**

Since there is no personal data processing there will not be any record of users or related to them. Otherwise you would enjoy your legal rights of access, correction, deletion and blocking of your data. 

**8\. Access to other sites**

Our service provides with links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you.
